Guide to the Columbia Unoversity Press Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Arranged Files
  - Mandel, Bernard (Box 145)
  - Mandel, Oscar (Box 145)
  - Mandelbaum, May (Box 145)
  - Mangone, Gerard J. (Box 145)
  - Mann - Map (Box 145)
  - Manning, Clarence Augustus (Box 145)
  - Manniche, Peter (Box 145)
  - Mantz, Harold Elmer (Box 145)
  - Mara - Mari (Box 145)
  - Marchand, Leslie A. (Box 145)
  - Marcus, Ralph (Box 145)
  - Marcy, Carl Milton (Box 145)
  - Margolin, Arnold Davidovich (Box 145)
  - Mark - Marl (Box 145)
  - Mark, Irving (Box 145)
  - Markoff, Eufrosina Dvoichenko (Box 145)
  - Marnell, William H. (Box 145)
  - Maro - Mars (Box 146)
  - Marraro, Howard Rosario (Box 146)
  - Marriott, Sir John Arthur Ransome (Box 146)
  - Marsh; Marshall (Box 146)
  - Marshall, Roderick (Box 146)
  - Marti -Marx (Box 146)
  - Martin (Box 146)
  - Martin, Galdys (Box 146)
  - Martin, James Alfred (Box 146)
  - Marvin, Walter Rumsey (Box 146)
  - Marvin, Walter Taylor (Box 146)
  - Mas (Box 147)
  - Masefield, John & Charles H. Simmons (Box 147)
  - Mason, Alexander Hamilton (Box 147)
  - Mason, Robert Emmett (Box 147)
  - Matc - Mats (Box 147)
  - Matchette, Franklin J., Foundation, Inc. (Box 147)
  - Matenko, Percy (Box 147)
  - Mathematical tables project (Box 147)
  - Matheson Commission: epidemic encephalitis (Box 147)
  - Mathews, Andrew Jackson (Box 147)
  - Mathisen, Trygve (Box 147)
  - Matt - Matz (Box 148)
  - Matthews, Brander (Box 148)
  - Mau (Box 148)
  - May-Maz (Box 148)
  - Mayer (Box 148)
  - Mayer, J. Peter (Box 148)
  - Mayer, Joseph (Box 148)
  - Mayer, Kurt Bernd (Box 148)
  - Mayo-Smith, Richmond (Box 148)
  - Mayr, Ernst (Box 148)
  - Mazza, Maria Serafina (Box 148)
  - Mea - Med (Box 148)
  - Mead, Margaret (Box 148)
  - Meade, Edward Grant (Box 148)
  - Meder, Elsa Marie (Box 148)
  - Meek, Wilbur Thornton (Box 148)
  - Meh - Mej (Box 149)
  - Meier, Hermann (Box 149)
  - Meighen, Arthur (Box 149)
  - Mel - Men (Box 149)
  - Melbourne University Press (Box 149)
  - Melman, Seymour (Box 149)
  - Menger, Louis Emil (Box 149)
  - Menges, Karl Heinrich (Box 149)
  - Mer (Box 149)
  - Mercer,Samuel Alfred Browne (Box 149)
  - Merlin, Sidney Daniell (Box 149)
  - Meriden Gravure Company (Box 149)
  - Merington, Marguerite (Box 149)
  - Merriam, Charles Edward (Box 149)
  - Merriam, Harold Guy (Box 149)
  - Merton, Egon Stephen (Box 149)
  - Mes - Met (Box 149)
  - Mesick, Jane Louise (Box 149)
  - Mespoulet, Marguerite (Box 149)
  - Messitte, Blanche (Box 149)
  - Messer, William Stuart (Box 149)
  - Mey (Box 149)
  - Meyer, Gladys Eleanor (Box 149)
  - Meyer, Martin Abraham (Box 149)
  - Meyer, Robert, Jr. (Box 149)
  - Mic (Box 149)
  - Mid - Mig (Box 149)
  - Mierow, Charles Christopher (Box 149)
  - Milb - Milj (Box 150)
  - Miles, Dudley Howe (Box 150)
  - Mill, John Stuart (Box 150)
  - Milla - Millh; Miller (Box 150)
  - Miller, Alice Duer & Susan Myers (Box 150)
  - Miller, Edward Frederick (Box 150)
  - Miller, Henry Siefke (Box 150)
  - Miller, Joseph Hillis (Box 150)
  - Miller, Spencer (Box 150)
  - Miller, William (Box 150)
  - Millett, John David (Box 150)
  - Milli - Mim (Box 150)
  - Millington, Herbert (Box 150)
  - Millner, Simon L. (Box 150)
  - Mills (Box 150)
  - Mills, Clarence A. (Box 150)
  - Mills, Edward Lloyd (Box 150)
  - Milton, John (Box 151 & 152)
  - Min - Mis (Box 153)
  - Mindil, Clinton (Box 153)
  - Miner, Dwight Carroll (Box 153)
  - Miriam, Joseph, Sr. See: Rauh (Box 153)
  - Mirkine-Guetzevitch, Boris (Box 153)
  - Missall, John Ellswerth (Box 153)
  - Mit - Miz (Box 153)
  - Mitchell (Box 153)
  - Mitchell, Julia Post (Box 153)
  - Mitchell, Samuel Alfred (Box 153)
  - Mitchell, Wesley Clair (Box 153)
  - Moc-Mof (Box 154)
  - Mohl, Ruth (Box 154)
  - Mohn - Mom (Box 154)
  - Moir, Thomas L. (Box 154)
  - Molk, Sophia (Box 154)
  - Mon (Box 154)
  - Moncreiffe, William (Box 154)
  - Monges, Richard Gladwin (Box 154)
  - Monroe (Box 154)
  - Montagu, Ashley (Box 154)
  - Montgomery, James A. (Box 154)
  - Mood - Moon (Box 155)
  - Moody, Herbert R. (Box 155)
  - Moore (Box 155)
  - Moore, Clement Clarke (Box 155)
  - Moore, Frank Gardner (Box 155)
  - Moore, John Bassett & Edwin Borchard (Box 155)
  - Moore, Justin Hartley (Box 155)
  - Moore, William Dyer (Box 155)
  - Mooreh - Moos (Box 155)
  - Mora - More (Box 155)
  - Morawetz, Victor (Box 155)
  - Morey, T., & Son (Box 155)
  - Morgan, Arthur Ernest (Box 155)
  - Morgan, Charlotte Elizabeth (Box 156)
  - Morgan, D. - Morgan, O. (Box 156)
  - Morgan, John William (Box 156)
  - Morgan, Thomas Hunt (Box 156)
  - Morgen - Morn (Box 156)
  - Morice, John H. (Box 156)
  - Morison; Morrill; Morris; Morrison (Box 156)
  - Morlan, George Kolmer (Box 156)
  - Morley, Edith J. (Box 156)
  - Morr (Box 156)
  - Morris, Richard Brandon (Box 156)
  - Morrison, A. Cressy (Box 156)
  - Morse, James King (Box 156)
  - Morse.. (Box 156)
  - Mort, Paul P. & Francis G. Cornell (Box 157)
  - Morton, Dudley Joy (Box 157)
  - Morton, W. W., Vernon H. Gaston, & Herrick K. L idstone (Box 157)
  - Morwitz, Ernst (Box 157)
  - Mos - Mot (Box 157)
  - Mosher, Joseph Albert (Box 157)
  - Mosier, Richard David (Box 157)
  - Mossner, Ernest Campbell (Box 157)
  - Most, Harry (Box 157)
  - Mou - Ms (Box 157)
  - Muc - Mui (Box 158)
  - Mudge, Eugene Tenbroeck (Box 158)
  - Mul (Box 158)
  - Mulholland, Mary Ambrose (Box 158)
  - Muller, Charlotte Feldman (Box 158)
  - Muller, Siegfried (Box 158)
  - Mullett, Charles Frederic (Box 158)
  - Mumford, Lewis (Box 158)
  - Mun - Mur (Box 158)
  - Munitz, Milton Karl (Box 158)
  - Munroe, Ruth Learned (Box 158)
  - Murad, Anatol (Box 158)
  - Muret, Charlotte Touzalin (Box 158)
  - Murgotten, Francis Clark (Box 158)
  - Murphy (Box 158)
  - Murphy, Frank (Box 158)
  - Murphy, Joseph M. (Box 158)
  - Murphy, Lois Barclay (Mrs Gardner) & Henry Ladd (Box 159)
  - Murra, John V., Robert M. Hankin & Fred Holling (Box 159)
  - Murray; Murry (Box 159)
  - Murray, Francis Joseph (Box 159)
  - Murray, Gilbert (Box 159)
  - Murray, Nicholas (Box 159)
  - Mus. (Box 160)
  - Muses, Charles Arthur (Box 160)
  - Mustard, Helen Meredith (Box 160)
  - Mustard, Wilfred Pirt (Box 160)
  - My (Box 160)
  - Myers (Box 160)
  - Myers, Bernard S. (Box 160)
  - Myers, Henry Alonzo (Box 160)
  - Myers, Margaret Good (Box 160)
  - Nag - Nath (Box 160)
  - Natanson, Maurice (Box 160)
  - Nathanson, Jerome (Box 160)
  - National A. - National C. (Box 160)
  - National Broadcasting Company (Box 160)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 160)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene (Box 160)
  - National Conference of Social Work, 1934-1951 (Box 161 & 162)
  - National G - National Y (Box 163)
  - National Interfaith Committee (Box 163)
  - National Labor Relations Board (Box 163)
  - National Municipal League (Box 163)
  - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness (Box 163)
  - Nato - Naz (Box 163)
  - Nea - Neh (Box 163)
  - Needles, Cora Blanche (Box 163)
  - Neely, Twila E. (Box 163)
  - Neely, Wayne Cladwell (Box 163)
  - Nef, Karl (Box 163)
  - Neff, Emery Edward (Box 163)
  - Neff, Wanda Fraiken (Mrs Emery) (Box 163)
  - Nelson (Box 164)
  - Nelson, Charles Alexander (Box 164)
  - Nelson, Margaret Virginia (Box 164)
  - Nelson, William A. (Box 164)
  - Nem - Nev (Box 164)
  - Nesbit, William Marsiglia (Box 164)
  - Nesbitt, George Lyman (Box 164)
  - Nettl, Paul (Box 164)
  - Nevins, Allan (Box 164)
  - Newa-Newc (Box 165)
  - Newcomer, Lee Nathaniel (Box 165)
  - Newcomer, Mabel (Box 165)
  - New copy; stories and. sketches.. (Box 165)
  - New Friends of Music Inc. (Box 165)
  - Newhall, Richard Ager & Jean Birdsall (Box 165)
  - Newl - New W (Box 165)
  - Newlin, Dika (Box 165)
  - Newman, Louis Israel (Box 165)
  - Newstead, Helaine H. (Box 165)
  - Newton, Roger Hale (Box 165)
  - New York Academy of Medicine (Box 166 & 167)
  - New York Al - New York U (Box 168)
  - New York School of Social Work (Box 168)
  - New York State Historical Association (Box 169 & 170)
  - Nib - Nic (Box 171)
  - Nie (Box 171)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold (Box 171)
  - Niebyl, Karl Heinrich (Box 171)
  - Nielsen, Aksel Evald. (Box 171)
  - Nietmann, William D. (Box 171)
  - Nik - Niz (Box 171)
  - Nilsson, Martin Persson (Box 171)
  - Nissenson, Samuel George (Box 171)
  - Nitchie, Elizabeth (Box 171)
  - Nixon, Howard Kenneth (Box 171)
  - Nob - Noo (Box 171)
  - Nobbe, George (Box 171)
  - Noether, Emiliana Pasca (Box 171)
  - Norb - Norr (Box 172)
  - Normano, John F. (Box 172)
  - North (Box 172)
  - Northrop, John Howard, Moses Kunitz, & Roger Moss Herriott (Box 172)
  - Norto - Not (Box 172)
  - Norton, Matthew F. (Box 172)
  - Nottingham, Elizabeth Kristine (Box 172)
  - Nov - Now (Box 172)
  - Novick, David, Melvin Leon Anshen, & William C. Truppner (Box 172)
  - Noyes, Charles Reinold (Box 172)
  - Nu - Ny (Box 172)
  - Nussbaum, Arthur (Box 172)
  - Nystrom, Paul Henry (Box 172)
  - Oakes, E Thomas (Box 173)
  - Ob (Box 173)
  - Oberndorf, Clarence P. (Box 173)
  - O'Brien, Justin (Box 173)
  - O'Brien, Mae (Box 173)
  - Oc (Box 173)
  - O'Connor, Mary Catharine (Box 173)
  - O'Connor, Mary E. (Box 173)
  - O'Connor, Michael Joseph Lalor (Box 173)
  - Od (Box 174)
  - Odegard, Peter H. (Box 174)
  - Odell, George Clinton Densmore (1) (Box 174)
  - Odell, George Clinton Densmore (2) (Box 175)
  - Oe - Of (Box 175)
  - Oetteking, Bruno (Box 175)
  - Og - Ok (Box 175)
  - Ogburn, William Fielding & William Jaffe (Box 175)
  - Ogden, Charles Jones (Box 175)
  - Ogdon, Montell E. (Box 175)
  - Ohlin, Bertil Gotthard (Box 175)
  - Okubo, Mine (Box 175)
  - Olc - Old (Box 175)
  - Olcott, George N. (Box 175)
  - Oli - Olp (Box 175)
  - Oliver, Alfred Richard (Box 175)
  - Ols (Box 175)
  - Olschki, Leonardo, Ruth J. Dean, & E.S. Doane (Box 175)
  - Om (Box 175)
  - On - Op (Box 175)
  - Onipede, F. Olapido (Box 175)
  - Or (Box 176)
  - Orchard, John Ewing (Box 176)
  - Ordan, Harry (Box 176)
  - Organ, Troy (Box 176)
  - O'Rourke, Vernon A & Douglas W. Campbell (Box 176)
  - Orton, Vrest (Box 176)
  - Os (Box 176)
  - Osborn, James Marshall (Box 176)
  - Osborne, Nancy Fontaine (Box 176)
  - Osgood, Herbert Levi (Box 176)
  - Oshima, Masanori (Box 176)
  - Ostheimer, Richard H. (Box 176)
  - Oswald, John Clyde (Box 176)
  - Ot (Box 176)
  - Otte, Herman Frederick (Box 176)
  - Ou - Ow (Box 176)
  - Owen, Clarence J. & Edward Page Gaston (Box 176)
  - Qwre, Alfred (Box 176)
  - Oxford University Press (Box 176)
  - Pab-Pag (Box 177)
  - Pabst, William Richard (Box 177)
  - Page, Eugene Richard (Box 177)
  - Pai - Pam (Box 177)
  - Palmer, Norman D. (Box 177)
  - Pan - Pap (Box 177)
  - Pancoast, Omar (Box 177)
  - Pap, Arthur (Box 177)
  - Pap, Leo (Box 177)
  - Para - Pari (Box 177)
  - Paris, James Daniel (Box 177)
  - Park; Parker (Box 177)
  - Parker, Arthur Caswell (Box 177)
  - Parker, Coralie (Box 177)
  - Parker, Fan (Box 177)
  - Parki - Parn (Box 177)
  - Parr - Pas (Box 178)
  - Parry, John Jay (Box 178)
  - Parsons (Box 178)
  - Parsons, Elsie Worthington Clews (Mrs Herbert) (Box 178)
  - Parsons, William Barclay (Box 178)
  - Pastore, Nicholas (Box 178)
  - Pat (Box 178)
  - Patchell, Mary Frances Corinne (Box 178)
  - Patrick, Mary Mills (Box 178)
  - Patten, Marjorie (Box 178)
  - Patterson (Box 178)
  - Patterson, Charles H. (Box 178)
  - Patterson, Frank Allen (Box 178)
  - Patterson, Frances Taylor (Box 178)
  - Patterson, Samuel White (Box 178)
  - Pattison, Bruce (Box 178)
  - Pau. (Box 178)
  - Paul, Harry Gilbert (Box 178)
  - Pav - Paz (Box 179)
  - Pavry, Jal Dastur Cursetji (Box 179)
  - Payne (Box 179)
  - Payne, Robert (Box 179)
  - Payne, William Lytton (Box 179)
  - Pea (Box 179)
  - Peake, Cyrus Henderson (Box 179)
  - Pearce, Charles Albert (Box 179)
  - Pearson (Box 179)
  - Peaslee, Amos J. (Box 179)
  - Pec - Ped (Box 180)
  - Peckham, H. H. (Box 180)
  - Pee - Pem (Box 180)
  - Peers, Edgar Allison (Box 180)
  - Pei, Mario Andrew (Box 180)
  - Pelcovits, Nathan Albert (Box 180)
  - Pell, Elsie E. (Box 180)
  - Pen-Pep (Box 180)
  - Penn, Edgar Legare (Box 180)
  - Perc - Perl (Box 180)
  - Percival, Milton Oswin (Box 180)
  - Periain, Annina (Mrs George Henry Danton) (Box 180)
  - Perry, Edward Delavan (Box 180)
  - Perr - Pes (Box 180)
  - Pet - Pey (Box 180)
  - Petegorsky, David W. (Box 180)
  - Peters, Evelene (Box 180)
  - Petersen; Peterson (Box 180)
  - Pf (Box 181)
  - Pfatteicher, Carl F. (Box 181)
  - Pfeffer, Jay Alan (Box 181)
  - Pfeiler, Wilhelm Karl (Box 181)
  - Ph (Box 182)
  - Phelan, Edward Joseph (Box 182)
  - Philippart, George (Box 182)
  - Phillips (Box 182)
  - Phillips, James Emerson (Box 182)
  - Phillips, Ulrich Bonnell (Box 182)
  - Phinney, Archie (Box 182)
  - Pia - Pie (Box 182)
  - Pil - Pin (Box 182)
  - Pike, Robert E (Box 182)
  - Pingel, Martha Mary (Box 182)
  - Pinkham, Mildred Worth (Box 182)
  - Pinson, Koppel Shub (Box 182)
  - Pio - Pit (Box 182)
  - Pitkin, Walter Boughton & Robert F. Harrel (Box 182)
  - Pizzi, Aailcare, S. A. (Milan) (Box 182)
  - Pl (Box 182)
  - Plamenac, Dragan (Box 182)
  - Pleasants, Samuel Augustus (Box 182)
  - Pod - Pof (Box 183)
  - Poe, Edgar Allan (Box 183)
  - Pohl, Frederick Julius (Box 183)
  - Pol - Poo (Box 183)
  - Pollack, Seymour V. (Box 183)
  - Pollock, Sir Frederick (Box 183)
  - Pollock, James Kerr (Box 183)
  - Pomerantz, Sidney Irving (Box 183)
  - Pommer, Henry F. (Box 183)
  - Poor, Charles Lane (Box 183)
  - Pop - Por (Box 183)
  - Porter, Albert Ogden (Box 183)
  - Porterfield, Allen Wilson (Box 183)
  - Pos - Pou (Box 183)
  - Poull, Louise Elizabeth (Box 183)
  - Paw - Poz (Box 183)
  - Powderly, Terence Vincent (Box 183)
  - Powell, Chilton Latham (Box 183)
  - Powell, Garfield (Box 183)
  - Powers, Edwin, Gordon W. Allport, & Helen Witmer (Box 183)
  - Pra - Pre (Box 184)
  - Prasad, Kali (Box 184)
  - Pratt, Carroll Cornelius (Box 184)
  - Pratt, Waldo Selden (Box 184)
  - Prentis, Edmund Astley & Lazarus White (Box 184)
  - Preobrazhenskii, Aleksandr Grigorevich (Box 184)
  - Prescott, Hilda Frances Margaret (Box 184)
  - Preveden, Francis R. (Box 184)
  - Prezzolini, Giuseppe (Box 184)
  - Pri (Box 185)
  - Price, William Raleigh (Box 185)
  - Prime-Stevenson, Edward Irenaeus (Box 185)
  - Prince, Charles (Box 185)
  - Prince, John Dyneley (Box 185)
  - Prince, Samuel Henry (Box 185)
  - Princeton (Box 185)
  - Prior, Moody Erasmus (Box 185)
  - Pritchard, E.H. (Box 185)
  - Pritcher, J.L. (Box 185)
  - Pro - Ps (Box 185)
  - Proodian, Ralph (Box 185)
  - The Protestant Welfare Federation (Box 185)
  - Prouty, Charles Tyler (Box 185)
  - Przedpelski, Boleslaw Jozef (Box 185)
  - Pu - Py (Box 186)
  - Public Library Inquiry series (Box 186)
  - Puckett, Hugh Wiley (Box 186)
  - Puente, Julius I. (Box 186)
  - Puerto Rico Journal of Public Health and Tropical Medicine (Box 186)
  - Pueschel, Wilhelm (Box 186)
  - Pugh, Anne Reese (Box 186)
  - Pulitzer Prizes, 1943 & 1947 (Box 186)
  - Pulse of the Nation, 1938 (Box 186)
  - Punk, Edward G. (Box 186)
  - Punke, Harold Herman (Box 186)
  - Pusey, William Webb (Box 186)
  - Pyburn, Nita Katherine (Box 186)
  - Qua - Que (Box 186)
  - Quain, Buell H. (Box 186)
  - A Quarter Century of Learning (Box 186)
  - Quinlan, Maurice James (Box 186)
  - R - Rad (Box 187)
  - Radbruch, Gustav (Box 187)
  - Raddin, George Gates, Jr. (Box 187)
  - Radin, George (Box 187)
  - Radin, Max (Box 187)
  - Radio broadcasting (Box 187)
  - Radomski, Alexander Leopold (Box 187)
  - Raesly, Ellis Lawrence (Box 187)
  - Raf - Ram (Box 187)
  - Rafferty, J.A. (Box 187)
  - Raine, Philip (Box 187)
  - Raiziss, Sonia (Box 187)
  - Ramon y Cajal, Santiago & Fernando de Castro (Box 187)
  - Ramsey, Carl T. (Box 187)
  - Ran (Box 187)
  - Rand, Harold S. (Box 187)
  - Randel, William Peirce (Box 187)
  - Randolph, Vance (Box 187)
  - Rap (Box 188)
  - Rapaport, David (Box 188)
  - Rappleye, Willard Cole (Box 188)
  - Ras - Rat (Box 188)
  - Rascher Verlag Zurich (Box 188)
  - Raser, George B. (Box 188)
  - Rasey, Marie I. (Box 188)
  - Ratchford, Fannie Elizabeth (Box 188)
  - Rathborne, Isabel Elizabeth (Box 188)
  - Rauch, Basil (Box 188)
  - Raudenbush, Henry William, Jr. (Box 188)
  - Rauh, Sr. Miriam Joseph (Box 188)
  - Raushenbush, Esther (Box 188)
  - Rautenstrauch, Walter (Box 188)
  - Ray - Raz (Box 189)
  - Raven-Hart, R. (Box 189)
  - Ravitz, Abe C (Box 189)
  - Ray, Royal H. (Box 189)
  - Raymond, Dora Neill (Box 189)
  - Raymond, Irving Woodworth (Box 189)
  - Rea (Box 189)
  - Read, Conyers (Box 189)
  - Read, Georgia Willis (Box 189)
  - Read, Mary L. (Box 189)
  - Read, Thomas Thornton (Box 189)
  - Records of Civilization series (Box 190)
  - Rector, Elbridge S. (Box 190)
  - Red (Box 190)
  - Reddick, Lawrence D. (Box 190)
  - Reder, Melvin Warren (Box 190)
  - Redmond, Pauline (Box 190)
  - Redway, Virginia Larkin (Box 190)
  - Reece, Ernest James (Box 190)
  - Reed - Reep (Box 190)
  - Reed, Amy Louise (Box 190)
  - Reed, Ruth (Box 190)
  - Rees - Reey (Box 190)
  - Reeves, John K. (Box 190)
  - Reference Librarians, Committee of (Box 191)
  - Reflections on our age; lectures UNESCO (Box 191)
  - Rehabilitation of service men (Box 191)
  - Reic - Reid (Box 191)
  - Reichart, Gladys Amanda (Box 191)
  - Reichenbach, Herman R. (Box 191)
  - Reichert, Philip (Box 191)
  - Reid, Charles F. (Box 191)
  - Reid, Ira De Augustine (Box 191)
  - Reid, Leonard J. (Box 191)
  - Reik, Theodore (Box 191)
  - Reil - Rein (Box 191)
  - Reinhold, Meyer (Box 191)
  - Reis - Rem (Box 191)
  - Reitzels, C.A., Forlag (Copenhagen) (Box 191)
  - Remenyi, Joseph (Box 191)
  - Remsberg, Robert G. (Box 191)
  - Ren - Rex (Box 191)
  - Resner, Herbert (Box 191)
  - Resnick, Louis (Box 191)
  - Reyes, Alfonso (Box 191)
  - Reyher, Rebecca Hourwich (Box 191)
  - Reyn - Rh (Box 192)
  - Reynolds, Beatrice (Box 192)
  - Ribble, Frederick Deane Goodwin (Box 192)
  - Ribble, Margaretha Antoinette (Box 192)
  - Ricc - Rice (Box 192)
  - Ricci, James V. (Box 192)
  - Rice, George Philip, Jr. (Box 192)
  - Rice, Jessie Pearl (Box 192)
  - Rice, Lillian Lawson (Box 192)
  - Rich (Box 193)
  - Rich, John Lyon (Box 193)
  - Richard; Richards (Box 193)
  - Richards, Edward Ames (Box 193)
  - Richardson (Box 193)
  - Richardson, Chalmer O. (Box 193)
  - Richardson, Cyril Charles (Box 193)
  - Richardson, Leon Burr (Box 193)
  - Richardson, Lyon N. (Box 193)
  - Richm - Rick (Box 193)
  - Richter, I.S. (Box 193)
  - Rickert, Edith, Clair Colby Olson & Martin Michael Crow (Box 193)
  - Rid - Rig (Box 194)
  - Riddell, William Renwick (Box 194)
  - Ridgeway, George L. (Box 194)
  - Riedel, Frederick Carl (Box 194)
  - Rienow, Robert (Box 194)
  - Riess, Ernst (Box 194)
  - Rife, David C. (Box 194)
  - Riggs, Fred Warren (Box 194)
  - Ril-Rip (Box 194)
  - Riley, John W.L, Jr (Box 194)
  - Ripka, Hubert (Box 194)
  - Ris - Riv (Box 194)
  - Ristine, Frank Humphrey (Box 194)
  - Roa (Box 194)
  - Rob - Robe (Box 194)
  - Robb, Mary Margaret (Box 194)
  - Robbins, J. Albert (Box 194)
  - Robbins, Rainard Benton (Box 194)
  - Robbins, Russell Hope (Box 194)
  - Roberts, David E. (Box 194)
  - Roberts, Hazel Van Dyke (Box 194)
  - Robertson, D.B. (Box 194)
  - Robey, Ralph W. (Box 194)
  - Robi (Box 195)
  - Robinson (Box 195)
  - Robinson, Claude E. (Box 195)
  - Robinson, Duane Morris (Box 195)
  - Robinson, Dwight Edwards (Box 195)
  - Robinson, George Buchan (Box 195)
  - Robinson, Howard (Box 195)
  - Robinson, James Harvey (Box 195)
  - Robinson, Thomas Porter (Box 195)
  - Robinson, William S. (Box 195)
  - Robison, Sophia Moses (Box 195)
  - Robson, John William (Box 196)
  - Robson, W.A. (Box 196)
  - Roc - Rod (Box 196)
  - Rocker, Rudolf (Box 196)
  - Rodick, Burleigh Cushing (Box 196)
  - Roe - Rog (Box 196)
  - Roessler, Erwin William Eugene (Box 196)
  - Rogers (Box 196)
  - Rogers, Bruce (Box 196)
  - Rogers, Elizabeth Frances (Box 196)
  - Rogers, James Harver (Box 196)
  - Rogers, Lindsay (Box 196)
  - Roh - Rol (Box 197)
  - Rojas, Ricardo (Box 197)
  - Rom - Rop (Box 197)
  - Rood, Roland (Box 197)
  - Rooker, H.G. (Box 197)
  - Root, Winthrop K (Box 197)
  - Ros - Rosel (Box 197)
  - Rosa, Matthew Whiting (Box 197)
  - Rosander, A.C. (Box 197)
  - Rose (Box 197)
  - Rose, Ernestine (Box 197)
  - Rosen - Rosh (Box 197)
  - Rosen, Edward (Box 197)
  - Rosen, S. McKee (Box 197)
  - Rosenberg, Stuart E. (Box 197)
  - Rosenblatt, Samuel (Box 197)
  - Rosenblum, Leo (Box 197)
  - Rosett, Joshua (Box 197)
  - Rositske, Harry August (Box 198)
  - Roso (Box 198)
  - Ross (Box 198)
  - Ross, Frank Alexander & Louise Venable Kennedy (Box 198)
  - Ross, Frank E. (Box 198)
  - Ross, J.F.S. (Box 198)
  - Rosso, Sisto (Box 198)
  - Rot - Rou (Box 198)
  - Rotenstreich, Nathan (Box 198)
  - Roth, Ernest David (Box 198)
  - Rothenberg, Alan Baer (Box 198)
  - Routledge, George, and Sons Ltd. (London) (Box 198)
  - Row - Roz (Box 198)
  - Rowen, Ruth Halle (Box 198)
  - Rowley, Scott (Box 198)
  - Rub - Rud (Box 198)
  - Rubin, Samuel (Box 198)
  - Rudman, Harry William (Box 198)
  - Rudolph, Harold J. (Box 198)
  - Rue - Run (Box 198)
  - Rufener, Helen Beatrice La Rue (Box 198)
  - Rugoff, Milton (Box 198)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel (Box 198)
  - Rumney, Jay (Box 198)
  - Rusack, Hedwig Hoffman (Box 199)
  - Rusb - Rusk (Box 199)
  - Rusche, Georg & Otto Kirchheimer (Box 199)
  - Rush, John A. (Box 199)
  - Rusk, Ralph Leslie (Box 199)
  - Russell (Box 200)
  - Russell, James Earl (Box 200)
  - Russell, Josiah C. (Box 200)
  - Russell, Trusten Wheeler (Box 200)
  - Russell, William Fletcher (Box 200)
  - Russell, William Logie (Box 200)
  - Russian series (Box 200)
  - Russian Translation Project (Box 200)
  - Russm - Rut (Box 200)
  - Russo, Joseph Louis (Box 200)
  - Rutenber, Culbert Gerow (Box 200)
  - Rutgers University (Box 200)
  - Rutledge, Anna Wells (Box 200)
  - Rutter, Owen (Box 200)
  - Ruutz-Rees, Caroline (Box 200)
  - Ry.. (Box 200)
  - The Ryerson Press (Toronto) (Box 200)
  - Saa- Sag (Box 200)
  - Sackett, Henry Woodward (Box 200)
  - Sackton, Alexander Hart (Box 200)
  - Sadleir, Michael (Box 200)
  - Saerchinger, Cesar (Box 200)
  - Sah - Sak (Box 200)
  - Saintsbury, George Edward Bateman (Box 200)
  - Sal. (Box 200)
  - Salomon-Delatour, Gottfried (Box 200)
  - Salzman, Marcus (Box 200)
  - Sam. (Box 200)
  - San - Sande (Box 201)
  - Sanchez, George Isidore (Box 201)
  - Sanderson, Gorham D. (Box 201)
  - Sandi - Sap (Box 201)
  - Sanford, Eva Matthews (Box 201)
  - Saposs, David Joseph (Box 201)
  - Sar - Sau (Box 201)
  - Sarachek, Joseph (Box 201)
  - Sarah Lawrence College Publications (Box 201)
  - Saul, George Brandon (Box 201)
  - Saulnier, Raymond Joseph (Box 201)
  - Sav (Box 201)
  - Savelle, Max (Box 201)
  - Saveth, Edward Norman (Box 201)
  - Saw-Say (Box 201)
  - Sayre, Mr. & Mrs. Leslie C. (Box 201)
  - Sca (Box 202)
  - Scanlan, Joseph J. (Box 202)
  - Scarborough, Dorothy (Box 202)
  - Scarry, Joseph T. (Box 202)
  - Scenna, Anthony (Box 202)
  - Schaa - Schad (Box 202)
  - Schachner, Nathan (Box 202)
  - Schaf - Schau (Box 202)
  - Schafer, Mark (Box 202)
  - Schaffner, Bertram Henry (Box 202)
  - Schaffter, Dorothy (Box 202)
  - Schapiro, Jacob Salwyn (Box 202)
  - Scharfstein, Ben-Ami (Box 202)
  - Schargo, Nelly Noemie (Box 202)
  - Sche. (Box 202)
  - Schecter, Frank Isaacs (Box 202)
  - Schenck, Martin (Box 202)
  - Scheyer, Ernst (Box 202)
  - Schi. (Box 203)
  - Schifferes, Justus J. (Box 203)
  - Schilder, Paul F. (Box 203)
  - Schiller, Ferdinand Canning Scott (Box 203)
  - Schiller, Paul H. (Box 203)
  - Schilling, Bernard Nicholas (Box 203)
  - Schinnerer, Otto Paul (Box 203)
  - Schl. (Box 203)
  - Schleiter, Frederick (Box 203)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Meier (Box 203)
  - Schlieder, Frederick William (Box 203)
  - Schm. (Box 203)
  - Schmidt, Carl Theodore (Box 203)
  - Schmidt, George Paul (Box 203)